let questions=[
	{
		numb:1,
		question:"Web page editors works on a ____ principle",
		answer:"WYSIWYG",
		options:[
			"WWW",
			"HTML",
			"WYSIWYG",
			"WYGWYSI"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:2,
		question:"Which program is used by web clients to view the web pages?",
		answer:"Web browser",
		options:[
			"Web browser",
			"Protocol",
			"Web server",
			"Search Engine"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:3,
		question:"What is the name of the location address of the hypertext documents?",
		answer:"Uniform Resource Locator",
		options:[
			" Uniform Resource Locator",
			"Web server",
			"File",
			"Web address"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:4,
		question:"What are shared on the Internet and are called as Web pages?",
		answer:"Hypertext documents",
		options:[
			"Programs",
			"Cables",
			"Hypertext documents",
			"None"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:5,
		question:"Which tag is used to display text in title bar of a web document?",
		answer:"Title tag",
		options:[
			"Body tag",
			"Meta tag",
			"Title tag",
			"Comment tag"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:6,
		question:"The language that instructs the browser on how to display the hypertext, and adds pictures to the document is __",
		answer:"HTML",
		options:[
			"C",
			"COBOL",
			"HTML",
			" BASIC"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:7,
		question:"The ____ attribute is used to identify the values of variables?",
		answer:" content",
		options:[
			"content",
			" http-equiv",
			"text",
			" name"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:8,
		question:"Which are used with a tag to modify its function?",
		answer:" Attributes",
		options:[
			"Documents",
			"Files",
			"Functions",
			" Attributes"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:9,
		question:"Which tag is used to identify the keywords describing the site?",
		answer:"Meta tag",
		options:[
			"Comment tag",
			"Title tag",
			" Anchor tag",
			"Meta tag"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:10,
		question:"The CELLSPACING attribute is used to ___",
		answer:"Specify the space between cells",
		options:[
			"Specify the colour of the border",
			"Specify the space between cells",
			"Specify the thickness of the border",
			" Specify the space between text and border"
		]
	},
];